[{"answer": "What? No good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Faux pas", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Uptight? Let's all just have a big pee party. Hey everybody, grab a bucket. We're going up to my friend's. It's a pee party.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hello. Yeah, hi, this is my friend calling for my friend. Hello? Hi? Uh huh, really, uh, no problem, definitely, ok, buhbye. That was my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "When", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Right now?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "\"Jerr", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He wants to talk about", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "He wants to talk about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "\"Jerr", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Don't worry, don't worry, no scenes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I will not blow this", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How you been", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, good to see you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, good to see you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You remember my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You remember my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "This is my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The that place guy liked it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He told you he liked it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, what are you doing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You know how to write", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, only for a while", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I'll be back", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's still bleak", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You can be bleak in spring", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "All right! You know what, just forget it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'll go to that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It's effeminate to sit like this", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How is this effeminate", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "my friend, what are you doing", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Great", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah, my friend got something I want to say to you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "We'll see you later.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I say we go back to that place, and take a regular flight", "qsentId": 36}]